A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Indian burning fields, poison fields, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-1 (2 OF 2)
- Fairfax County is formed, General Assembly document, 1978; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-2 (1 OF 2)
- Fairfax County is formed, General Assembly document, 1978; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-2 (2 OF 2)
- Willicoxon Tavern and Hague's House at Back, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-3 (1 OF 2)
- Willicoxon Tavern and Hague's House at Back, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-3 (2 OF 2)
- Willicoxon Tavern, 1978; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-4 (1 OF 2)
- Willicoxon Tavern, 1978; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-4 (2 OF 2)
- Earp Survey, Store at Courthouse, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-5 (1 OF 2)
- Earp Survey, Store at Courthouse, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-5 (2 OF 2)
- George Washington Will, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-6 (2 OF 2)
- 1804 Plat of Town of Fairfax, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-7 (1 OF 2)
- 1805 Plat of Town of Fairfax, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-7 (2 OF 2)
- Virginia General Assembly, establishes town of Providence (now Fairfax), Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-8 (1 OF 2)
- Virginia General Assembly, establishes town of Providence (now Fairfax), Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-8 (2 OF 2)
- Lots built on Lot 10- Line 12, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-9 (1 OF 2)
- Lots built on Lot 10- Line 13, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-9 (2 OF 2)
- Layout of Fairfax City (Providence) when founded, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-10 (1 OF 2)
- Layout of Fairfax City (Providence) when founded, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-10 (2 OF 2)
- Record of secession votes, voting at Fairfax Courthouse, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-11 (1 OF 2)
- Record of secession votes, voting at Fairfax Courthouse, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-11 (2 OF 2)
- Plat of Ratcliffe Division about 1835, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-12 (1 OF 2)
- Plat of Ratcliffe Division about 1835, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-12 (2 OF 2)
- Henry Clay letter at Fairfax Court House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-13 (1 OF 2)
- Henry Clay letter at Fairfax Court House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-13 (2 OF 2)
- Map of Manassas Gap Railroad's proposed route through Fairfax, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-14 (1 OF 2)
- Manassas Gap Fairfax City, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-14 (2 OF 2)
- 1878 map of Fairfax City, Hopkins Atlas, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-15 (1 OF 2)
- 1879 map of Fairfax City, Hopkins Atlas, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-15 (2 OF 2)
- Fairfax City map by Courtland Davis about 1920, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-16 (1 OF 2)
- Fairfax City map by Courtland Davis about 1920, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-16 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, Ratcliffe-Logan-Allison House, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-17 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, Ratcliffe-Logan-Allison House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-17 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-18 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-18 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, living room, old part, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-19 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, living room, old part, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-19 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, living room addition, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-20 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, living room addition, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-20 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, original part, 1805, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-21 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, original part, 1805, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-21 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, newer half, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-22 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, newer half, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-22 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, showing star bolts, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-23 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, showing star bolts, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-23 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, close up of cornice and brick, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-24 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, close up of cornice and brick, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-24 (2 OF 2)
- Winchester and Alexandria Mail Stage, Bill to Allison Way, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-25 (1 OF 2)
- Winchester and Alexandria Mail Stage, Bill to Allison Way, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-25 (2 OF 2)
- Dr. Kate Waller Barrett, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-26 (1 OF 2)
- Dr. Kate Waller Barrett, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-26 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, 1923 Fairfax Herald article, Box 2: FXCI-RUST-27 (1 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary, 1923 Fairfax Herald article, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-27 (2 OF 2)
- Plat of Lot 10, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-28 (1 OF 2)
- Plat of Lot 10, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-28 (2 OF 2)
- Earp's Ordinary circa 1870, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-29
- Shoe Buckle c. 1775-1800 found at Earp's Ordinary, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-30 (1 OF 2)
- Shoe Buckle c. 1775-1800 found at Earp's Ordinary, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-30 (2 OF 2)
- Capt. John Marr, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-31 (1 OF 2)
- Capt. John Marr, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-31 (2 OF 2)
- Ex- Governor Billy Smith, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-32 (1 OF 2)
- Ex- Governor Billy Smith, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-32 (2 OF 2)
- Col. Richard S. Ewell, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-33 (1 OF 2)
- Col. Richard S. Ewell, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-33 (2 OF 2)
- Col. Richard S. Ewell's Epaulet, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-34 (1 OF 2)
- Col. Richard S. Ewell's Epaulet, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-34 (2 OF 2)
- Gen. Edwin Stoughton, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-35 (1 OF 2)
- Gen. Edwin Stoughton, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-35 (2 OF 2)
- Mosby captures Stoughton, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-36 (1 OF 2)
- Tomkins Retrieves Men at Fairfax Court House, Pictorial War Record, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-37 (1 OF 2)
- Tomkins Retrieves Men at Fairfax Court House, Pictorial War Record, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-37 (2 OF 2)
- Plat of Skirmish in Fairfax City, June 1, 1861, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-38 (1 OF 2)
- Plat of Skirmish in Fairfax City, June 1, 1862, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-38 (2 OF 2)
- John Marr Commemoration, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-39 (1 OF 2)
- Matthew Brady's "What-is-it" wagon, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-40 (1 OF 2)
- Matthew Brady's "What-is-it" wagon, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-40 (2 OF 2)
- Bailey's Crossroads, Sulter Chuck Wagon, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-41 (1 OF 2)
- Bailey's Crossroads, Sulter Chuck Wagon, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-41 (2 OF 2)
- Confederate Monument at Fairfax Cemetery, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-42
- Mosby Monument at Turo Church, Main Street, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-43 (1 OF 2)
- Mosby Monument at Turo Church, Main Street, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-43 (2 OF 2)
- Telephone, 1885, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-44 (1 OF 2)
- Telephone, 1885, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-44 (2 OF 2)
- Printing Press, 1882, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-45 (1 OF 2)
- Printing Press, 1883, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-45 (2 OF 2)
- Laura Ratcliffe, born in Fairfax City, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-46
- Presentation page of album from J.E.B. Stuart to Laura Ratcliffe, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-47 (1 OF 2)
- Presentation page of album from J.E.B. Stuart to Laura Ratcliffe, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-47 (2 OF 2)
- Album given by J.E.B. Stuart to Laura Ratcliffe, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-48 (1 OF 2)
- Album given by J.E.B. Stuart to Laura Ratcliffe, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-48 (2 OF 2)
- J.E.B. Stuart watch chain, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-49 (1 OF 2)
- J.E.B. Stuart watch chain, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-49 (2 OF 2)
- J.E.B. Stuart's dollar, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-50
- Cooper Carriage House, low white building in center is old Fairfax County Public Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-51 (1 OF 2)
- Cooper Carriage House, low white building in center is old Fairfax County Public Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-51 (2 OF 2)
- Love House, Coon Cottage School Building #1, raided by Union Army, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-52 (1 OF 2)
- Love House, Coon Cottage School Building #1, raided by Union Army, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-52 (2 OF 2)
- Coon Cottage #2, Swetnam Home, one story white building at left is old Fairfax County Public Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-53 (1 OF 2)
- Coon Cottage #2, Swetnam Home, one story white building at left is old Fairfax County Public Library, Undated'; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-53 (2 OF 2)
- Coon Cottage #3, Herring House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-54 (1 OF 2)
- Coon Cottage #3, Herring House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-54 (2 0F 2)
- Duncan's Chapel, Old Fairfax Methodist Church, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-55 (1 OF 2)
- Duncan's Chapel, Old Fairfax Methodist Church, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-55 (2 OF 2)
- Ford Building, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-56 (1 OF 2)
- Ford Building, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-56 (2 OF 2)
- Blenheim, Willcoxon home, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-57 (1 OF 2)
- Blenheim, Willcoxon home, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-57 (2 OF 2)
- Layton Hall, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-58 (1 OF 2)
- Layton Hall, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-58 (2 OF 2)
- Conrad Bower, Mrs. McCandlish House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-59 (1 OF 2)
- Conrad Bower, Mrs. McCandlish House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-59 (2 OF 2)
- Draper House, circa 1821, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-60 (1 OF 2)
- Draper House, circa 1821, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-60 (2 OF 2)
- D'Astra Tenement, Maine and Orchard, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-61 (1 of 2)
- D'Astra Tenement, Maine and Orchard, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-61 (2 of 2)
- D'Astra Tenement, window to concealed room, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-62 (1 of 2)
- D'Astra Tenement, window to concealed room, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-62 (2 of 2)
- Ratcliffe Graveyard, Moore Street, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-63 (1 of 2)
- Ratcliffe Graveyard, Moore Street, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-63 (2 of 2)
- Ratcliffe Race Track, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-64 (1 of 2)
- Ratcliffe Race Track, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-64 (2 of 2)
- Judge Thomas Tenement, porch posts from court house, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-65
- The Falls Church, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-66 (1 of 2)
- The Falls Church, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-66 (2 of 2)
- Oliver Building, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-67 (1 of 2)
- Oliver Building, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-67 (2 of 2)
- Nan's Cottage Blacksmith Shop, East Street, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-68 (1 of 2)
- Nan's Cottage Blacksmith Shop, East Street, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-68 (2 of 2)
- Five Chimneys, Ann Farr Lewis Home, descendent of Ratcliffe, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-69 (1 of 2)
- Five Chimneys, Ann Farr Lewis Home, descendent of Ratcliffe, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-69 (2 of 2)
- Elliot Home, Edith Farr Elliot, Ratcliffe descendent, E. Main Street, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-70 (1 of 2)
- Elliot Home, Edith Farr Elliot, Ratcliffe descendent, E. Main Street, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-70 (2 of 2)
- Zion Episcopal Church, burned during Civil War, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-71 (1 of 2)
- Zion Episcopal Church, burned during Civil War, 1973; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-71 (2 of 2)
- Truro Chapel, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-72
- One-half of Truro Rectory, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-73 (1 of 2)
- One-half of Truro Rectory, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-73 (2 of 2)
- Truro Episcopal Rectory, circa 1800, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-74 (1 of 2)
- Truro Episcopal Rectory, circa 1800, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-74 (2 of 2)
- Old Jerusalem Baptist Church, Payne's Church, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-75 (1 of 2)
- Old Jerusalem Baptist Church, Payne's Church, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-75 (2 of 2)
- Patrick Henry order, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-76 (1 of 2)
- Patrick Henry order, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-76 (2 of 2)
- Joshua Gunnell, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-77 (1 of 2)
- Joshua Gunnell, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-77 (2 of 2)
- Chilcott Hill, Ratcliffe Site, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-78 (1 of 2)
- Chilcott Hill, Ratcliffe Site, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-78 (2 of 2)
- Fairfax County Courthouse with Marr Monument, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-79 (1 of 2)
- Fairfax County Courthouse with Marr Monument, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-79 (2 of 2)
- Five Chimneys, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST- 80 (1 of 2)
- Five Chimneys, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-80 (2 of 2)
- Coon Cottage, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-81 (1 of 2)
- Coon Cottage, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-81 (2 of 2)
- Professional Building, one story white building at left is old Fairfax County Public Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-82 (1 of 2)
- Professional Building, one story white building at left is old Fairfax County Public Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-82 (2 of 2)
- D'Astra House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-83 (1 of 2)
- D'Astra House, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-83 (2 of 2)
- Barbour Tenement, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-84 (1 of 2)
- Barbour Tenement, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-84 (2 of 2)
- Marr Monument, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-85 (1 of 2)
- Marr Monument, Undated; Box 2: FXCI-RUST-85 (2 of 2)
- Fairfax County Courthouse, built 1800 (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 2: FXCO-CT-1
- Fairfax Courthouse, 1968; Box 2: FXCO-CT-3
- Fairfax Courthouse, 1968; Box 2: FXCO-CT-4
- Fairfax Courthouse and Marr Monument (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 2: FXCO-CT-5 (1 of 2)
- Fairfax Courthouse and Marr Monument (photo by Nan Netherton), 1973; Box 2: FXCO-CT-5 (2 of 2)
- Fairfax Courthouse and Marr Monument, 1976; Box 2: FXCO-CT-6
- Fairfax County Courthouse, arcade, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-CT-7
- Fairfax County Courthouse, addition, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-CT-8
- Fairfax County Courthouse, interior, 1976; Box 2: FXCO-CT-9
- Extension Division, County agent with cows, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-EX-1
- Old Fairfax County Jail (photo by Steve Behrens), 1976; Box 2: FX-CO-J-1
- Old Fairfax County Jail, 1976; Box 2: FX-CO-J-2
- FCPL, Inter-branch delivery, 1974; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-1
- Child with Fairfax County Public Library balloon, 1974; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-2
- FCPL, Voter registration card, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-3
- FCPL, Voter registration in library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-4
- FCPL, Plant clinic, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-5
- FCPL, patrons at circulation desk, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-6
- FCPL, patrons in library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-7
- FCPL, patrons using microfilm reader, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-8
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-1
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-2
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-3
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-4
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-5
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-6
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-7
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-8
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-9
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-10
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-11
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-12
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-13
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-14
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-15
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-16
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-17
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-18
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, Jack Herrity, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-19
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-20
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-21
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-22
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-23
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-24
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-25
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-26
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-27
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, BK and Author Lunch, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-28
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, BK and Author Lunch, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-29
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of FCPL, BK and Author Lunch, 1979; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-ANN-30
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-1
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-2
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-3
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-4
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-5
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-6
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-7
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-8
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-9
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-10
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-11
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-12
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-13
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-14
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-15
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-16
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-17
- Library Board Meeting, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOARD-18
- Last day of FCPL Bookmobile, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-1
- Last day of FCPL Bookmobile, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-2
- Last day of FCPL Bookmobile, Bob Camarca, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-3
- Last day of FCPL Bookmobile, Bob Camarca, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-4
- Last day of FCPL Bookmobile, Bob Camarca, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-5
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-6
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-7
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-8
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-9
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-10
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-11
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-12
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-13
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-14
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-15
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-16
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-17
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-18
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-19
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-20
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-21
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1975 September; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-22
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1979 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-23
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1979 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-24
- FCPL "Book Spot" Bookmobile, 1979 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-25
- FCPL Bookmobile at Sherwood, 1973 June; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BOOK-26
- Burke Centre Library, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BC-1
- Burke Centre Library, Burke Center Shopping Center sign, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BC-2
- Burke Centre Library, 1983 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-BC-3
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, Director Mary K. McCulloch, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-1
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, Cuba Curtice chairman of FCPL Library Board, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-2
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-3
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-4
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-5
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-6
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-7
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-8
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-9
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-10
- Bowman House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library reception, 1966; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-11
- Bowman House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library reception, 1966; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-12
- Bowman House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library reception, 1966; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-13
- Bowman House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library reception, 1966; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-14
- Heron House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library program, 1967; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-15
- Heron House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library program, 1967; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-16
- Heron House, Friends of the Carter Glass Library program, 1967; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-17
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-18
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-19
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-20
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-21
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-22
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-23
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-24
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-25
- Carter Glass Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-26
- Carter Glass Library, Dedication, 1966 April 17; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CG-27
- Centreville Library, Before opening, 1970 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-1
- Centreville Library, Before opening, 1970 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-2
- Centreville Library, Before opening, 1970 April; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-3
- Centreville Library, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-4
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-5
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-6
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-7
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-8
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-9
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-10
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-11
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-12
- Centreville Library, Opening Day, 1970 May; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-13
- Centreville Library, 1983; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-14
- Centreville Library, Supervisor Marie Travesky, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-15
- Centreville Library, Supervisor Marie Travesky, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-16
- Centreville Library, Supervisor Marie Travesky, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-17
- Centerville Library, Reading Room, 1983; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-18
- Centerville Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-19
- Centerville Library, Circulation Desk, 1983; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-20
- Centerville Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-21
- Centerville Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-22
- Centerville Library, Microfiche Reader, 1983; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-23
- Centerville Library, Magazine Rack, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-24
- Centerville Library, Magazine Rack, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-25
- Centerville Library, Children's Section, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-26
- Centerville Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-27
- Centreville Library, Supervisor Marie Travesky, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-28
- Centerville Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-29
- Centerville Library, 1983; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-30
- Centerville Library, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-31
- Centerville Library, Centreville Volunteer Fire Department event, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-32
- Centerville Library, Centreville Volunteer Fire Department event, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-33
- Centerville Library, Centreville Volunteer Fire Department event, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-34
- Centerville Library, Centreville Volunteer Fire Department event, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-CE-35
- Dolley Madison Library, 1971; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-1
- Dolley Madison Library, St. Pierre Systems Seminar, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-2
- Dolley Madison Library, St. Pierre Systems Seminar, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-3
- Dolley Madison Library, St. Pierre Systems Seminar, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-4
- Dolley Madison Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-5
- Dolley Madison Library, 1971; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-6